This is the story of Bridget and Annie,
who share a flat in London,
and the boys next door,
Nick and his friend Hector from Argentina.
Hector and Annie were in love,
but now things are not so good.
[Translated by 24hmedia.net]
Bridget has given up on love,
And Nick -  well, his mum loves him!
Stand by for Extra!
Hector.
-  Yes?
-  Please could you pass the salt?
Yes.
Hector.
Yes?
Please could you pass the pepper?
Of course.
Hector.
Let me guess.
Can I pass the sugar, coffee, tea?
Actually, I was going to say we should talk.
So, now you want to talk to me!
It's only been a week!
-  I was hurt!
-  Well, you hurt me too.
-  I didn't go out with Eunice!
Yes, you did! And you stayed out
till three o'clock in the morning!
There were other people there, too.
-  Who?
-  People who work on the programme.
You mean other women
who work on the programme.
Yes, and men -  why not, huh?
I knew it!
So, who is she?
-  Who?
-  The other woman.
There is no other woman!
Huh!
Annie, listen.
Excuse me.
Hello. Hi, Debbie.
How are you? Good.
OK, that'll be OK. Perfect! See you then.
Bye.
So, was that her?
-  Who?
-  Debbie. The other woman!
That was Debbie from the make- up department,
confirming my call time for tomorrow.
Some excuse!
-  Hector.
-  Yes.
Please could you pass me your fork?
Here, I'm going.
You can have my dinner!
You should have seen Eunice's face!
She was furious!
When Eunice gets angry,
she is a very scary lady!
Hello.
Yes.
Excuse me. No, no, to her...
Bye, Bridget.
All right, Hector. Bye.
Hola, Lola!
-  Guess what?
-  Prince William wants to marry you?
I know that! No, I've got a promotion!
That's nice.
Nice? Nice!
It's fantastic! I am editor of Channel 9 Live!
Eunice is no longer my boss!
Is that Hugh Grant?
It's Bridget Evans here.
Call me Gigi, editor of Channel 9 Live.
Are we still on for lunch at Claridge's today?
Fab! Ciao!
Eunice is so jealous!
Now, that is good news.
Annie, what are you doing?
I'm doing my own editing.
Why are you cutting up
photos of you and Hector?
Because Hector is no longer my boyfriend.
Really?
Why?
Because he is having an affair!
Really?! Who with?
Well, I thought it was Eunice,
but now I think it's Debbie.
Well, I just heard him on the phone to Lola.
Lola? Who's she?
Ha! Eunice, Debbie, Lola!
He's women mad!
It's fantastic!
I am editor of Channel 9 Live!
Hola, Lola!
I didn't go out with Eunice!
Yes, you did! And you stayed out
till three o'clock in the morning!
So, was that her?
-  Who?
-  Debbie. The other woman!
Hi, Nick.
What are you doing?
I am not doing, I am being.
What are you being?
-  Can't you guess?
-  A man on the toilet?
A Sumo wrestler?
Can't you see? I am an egg.
Of course, you are an egg.
Now, what sort of egg am I?
Hard- boiled.
-  Scrambled.
-  Scrambled?
-  Fried.
-  Nearly!
Poached!
Yeah, of course. You are a poached egg.
Yeah.
Well, you're making a mess on your bed!
Anyway, why are you being a poached egg?
It's my new acting class.
Total Being.
What are you next week? A piece of wood?
-  A piece of wood?
-  Yeah! Then it would be wooden acting!
Anyway, can poached eggs talk?
Don't be silly! Of course poached eggs can't talk.
No, no, I mean,
when you are
'being' a poached egg, can you talk?
Yeah.
Anyway, I want to stop now,
my arms are hurting.
So, what do you want to talk about?
It is Annie.
She thinks I am having an affair.
-  Who with?
-  Eunice.
-  And Debbie.
-  What?
Two women, Hector!
You cheeky thing!
But I am not!
-  So tell Annie then.
-  I have but she doesn't believe me.
-  Why not?
-  I don't know.
Excuse me.
Hola, Lola.
I'll take this outside.
How are you, Lola?
So, it's not Eunice,
it's not Debbie, could it be - Lola?
Stop, please!
I knew it!
It had to be a selfish man- driver!
Please, I have a voucher.
I- I am sorry, I've started, so I'll finish.
Look, I am Zeus, why are you so angry?
I'm not. I am just doing my job - Zeus!
People park on yellow lines and then are
surprised when they get a parking ticket!
There was this one guy today -
'Please, I have a voucher.'
No excuse!
Mind you, he was quite cute.
Nick.
Nick, are you OK?
Bridget! Oh, it's you, Hector.
Well, there's something wrong with Nick.
-  Well, I could have told you that!
-  No, he won't speak, he won't move.
I know. He is being a poached egg.
-  A what?
-  For his new acting class.
Hi, Nick.
[Translated by 24hmedia.net]
Let me guess.
You are being - a potato.
Do I look like a potato?
Yes. A couch potato!
What about a fish?
Yes, a frozen fish!
I am not a fish.
I...am...'Pain'.
You are a pain.
Yes, Nick is a pain!
No! I am 'Pain'.
Hurt, agony.
So, how was your first day as editor, Bridget?
What a day!
I had a very important meeting.
Big decisions to make.
Like which celebrities,
new programme ideas?
No, like which pen to use at my meeting?
Blue, black...
-  Which one did you choose?
-  Blue.
Bad choice.
You think so? Oh, no!
Eunice is so jealous of Bridget's new job,
she won't talk to anyone!
-  Not even you?
-  Not even me! It is great!
You don't want her to talk to you?
-  Really?
-  Really!
Oh, Annie, I hate it when we argue.
So do I.
-  I miss you.
-  I miss...
Hola, Lola.
Right. Two can play that game.
I am not doing, I am being.
A man on the toilet?
Yeah!
I am not a fish! I...am...'Pain'.
It's not Eunice,
it's not Debbie, could it be -  Lola?
Hola, Lola!
Look, I am Zeus. Why are you so angry?
I am just doing my job - Zeus!
-  Hello again.
-  Hello.
-  We meet again.
-  You're happier today.
Yes, I am now!
But I'm sorry...
I parked here, so you would come back.
You wanted to see me again?
You are so beautiful!
Well, I'm sorry
but I am going to have to give you...
-  No...
-  This!
My phone number.
Call me.
Who needs Hector?
Hi, Bridget.
What 'oh'?
I know -  Superman!
-  What?
-  I mean, Clark Kent.
You are being Clark Kent, for your acting class.
No. I'm not.
I'm long- sighted.
You're being long- sighted?
No.
I am long- sighted.
I need to wear glasses for reading.
They suit you.
Thank you.
So, why are you not at Channel 9 today?
I'm working from home today.
I've so much to do!
Bridget, what's the matter?
I can't do it! Eunice hates me!
Eunice hates everybody!
-  They all hate me!
-  No, they don't!
-  They all look at me!
-  Bridget, you are their boss.
I have to use the executive loo!
What's the matter with that?
I want to chat to all the girls!
Bridget...
you are one of the cleverest,
most beautiful women I know.
Really?
-  Well, who are the others?
-  What do you mean?
You said I was only one of the cleverest,
most beautiful girls you know.
Bridget! You can do this job.
Channel 9 needs you.
-  Thank you, Nick.
-  Hey, it was nothing.
You really look handsome in those glasses.
Hi, Annie.
Hi, Hector.
-  You look smart.
-  Yes, I am going to meet someone.
Annie, I have something to tell you.
Sorry.
Lola!
Vale. Si, si, ya voy.
Hasta luego.
'Annie, I have something to tell you.'
That he is going on a date with Lola!
That's what!
Nick, stop it! You're tickling me!
Hi, Annie. I didn't hear you come in.
Nick! Stop it!
Is everybody happy, apart from me?
Hello.
Zeus! Hi!
Well, of course I remember you!
A drink? Tonight?
Well, I'd love to.
Stop it! You're tickling me!
Zeus, meet my friends, Bridget and Nick.
-  Hi.
Well, hello, Zeus!
Annie, where did you find him?
Yeah, but he doesn't wear glasses,
though, does he?
We've had a lovely evening, haven't we, Zeus?
Wonderful, Annie.
Now I must say goodnight.
Please, first may I use your bathroom?
-  Certainly.
-  Thank you.
Zeus is such a gentle man.
He certainly is a man.
Hi.
Annie, I must talk to you.
What about? Your date with Lola?
My date with Lola?
Annie, Lola is a 60- year- old
chief executive for ATV.
-  What's ATV?
-  Argentinian Television.
And...
She wants me to return to Argentina
to present their number one show.
But I don't want to go.
I want to stay here - with you.
That's better.
Hector, this is...
Zeus, my new boyfriend.
We've had a lovely evening, haven't we!
Come on, I'll say goodbye to you downstairs!
So, Hector, will you take the job?
What do you think I should do, Annie?
So we must say goodbye
to our friends for now.
Will Hector stay, or go back to Argentina?
Will Annie go with him?
And will Nick ever give up on Bridget?
Extra - will the story continue?!
[Translated by 24hmedia.net]