Head and shoulders.
Knees and toes,
Knees and toes.
Eyes and mouth
and ears and nose.
Ears and nose...
Where are we?
We're in the garden.
What, your garden?
No, silly!
The palace garden.
Look!
There's Sylvia!
What's she doing?
She's doing her exercises.
Knees and nose,
knees and toes...
Quick!
Behind this thing!
-What thing?
-The statue.
-Are you all right?
-No, we aren't.
We're hungry.
Can we have some food, please?
Can I have a clock, please?
A clock?
Excuse me.
Yes. A clock.
He likes clocks.
Somebody's coming.
Who is it?
I don't know.
I can't see.
OK!
Oh, no! It's raining.
Look, wait over there.
-OK.
-See you this evening.
-When?
-Seven o'clock.
See you at seven this evening.
Seven o'clock. Right!
What's the time now?
It's eight o'clock.
Hello?
No, I'm busy.
I'm having breakfast.
It's one o'clock.
Hello?
No, I'm busy.
I'm having lunch.
It's seven o'clock.
Hello?
No, I'm busy.
I'm having dinner.
It's nine o'clock.
Hello?
No, I'm busy.
I'm having a bath.
It's ten o'clock.
Hello?
Busy?
No, I'm going to bed.
Good night!
One o'clock.
It's lunch-time.
It's lunch-time, dear.
I'm coming.
It's lunch-time, Sylvia.
I'm not very well.
Can I have lunch in my room?
What's the matter?
I've got a terrible headache.
A headache.
Stomachache.
Toothache.
Backache.
Come in.
What's the matter?
I've got a headache, doctor.
A headache? Take this.
Thank you, doctor.
Next!
What's the matter?
I've got stomachache, doctor.
Stomachache? Take this.
Thank you, doctor.
Next!
What's the matter?
I've got toothache, doctor.
Toothache? Take this.
Thank you, doctor.
Next!
What's the matter?
I've got backache, doctor.
Backache? Take this.
Thank you, doctor.
A headache?
Stay in your room, dear,
and have a rest.
Lunch for the Princess
in her room!
Sylvia isn't very well.
She's got a headache.
She's having lunch in her room.
-His.
-Her.
-Her knife.
-His knife.
-His fork.
-Her fork.
-Her glass.
-His glass.
-His plate.
-Her plate.
-Her bowl.
-His bowl.
-His crown.
-Her crown.
A headache!
Hello, Sylvia.
How are you now?
How am I?
I'm fine, thank you.
Where are you going?
I'm going to the swimming pool.
See you!
Have a nice swim, dear.
Hello, Sylvia.
How are you now?
-Feeling better?
I'm fine.
Good, good, good.
Where are you going?
I'm going to the tennis court.
-See you!
-Have a nice game, dear.
Sylvia's feeling better now.
She's playing tennis.
Playing tennis?
No, she isn't.
She's having a swim.
Hello, Mummy!
Hello, Daddy!
Bye!