How do you do?
I'm the King.
I'm the King of Gondoland.
How do you do?
I'm the Queen.
Hello.
I'm Princess Sylvia.
Oh, Sylvia! Sylvia!
Hello. I'm Bob.
I'm the gardener.
How do you do?
I'm Corvax.
Thank you, Corvax.
Hi! I'm Muzzy.
Big Muzzy.
-Good morning.
Good morning.
I'm Norman.
Good...
afternoon.
Good afternoon.
Good evening.
-Good night.
I'm strong.
I'm fat.
I'm fat. I'm fat.
I'm beautiful.
I'm clever.
I'm brave.
-Strong.
-Fat.
-Beautiful
-Clever.
And brave.
-You're strong.
-Yes, I am.
-And you're fat.
And she's beautiful.
Yes, she is.
He's brave.
And he's clever.
No, no!
I'm clever.
I'm clever. Clever.
Clever.
-Strong.
-Fat.
-Beautiful.
-Clever.
-And brave.
-Big.
I'm big.
Big Muzzy.
Big.
Small.
I'm Big Muzzy.
Big.
Small.
And I'm Big Muzzy.
I've got a bag.
A big bag.
I've got a map.
I've got a hamburger.
I've got a bike. A motorbike.
I've got a computer.
I've got a garden.
Look!
I've got plums.
I've got peaches.
I've got grapes.
I like plums.
I like peaches.
I like grapes.
And I like grapes.
Hello, Mummy.
Hello, Daddy.
Can I have a peach, please?
I like hamburgers.
Can I have a hamburger, please?
Here you are.
Thank you.
Can I have a salad, please?
Here you are.
Thank you.
Can I have a drink, please?
Here you are.
Thank you.
Can I have an ice-cream,
please?
Here you are.
Thank you.
Can I have a wash, please?
Can I have a peach please,
Daddy?
Yes. A peach!
-A peach.
-Thank you.
Can I have a plum
and some grapes, please?
Yes.
A plum and some grapes!
A plum and some grapes.
Thank you.
A plum - a peach - a grape.
A plum - a peach - some grapes.
A plum - a plum - a plum!
Three plums!
Jackpot!
Plums! Plums! Plums!
-Bob!
-Yes?
Trees!
Trees?
Yes. How many trees?
Count!
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven,
eight, nine, ten.
How many trees are there?
One,
two,
three,
four,
five,
six,
seven,
eight,
nine,
ten.
Bushes!
How many bushes
are there?
There are two - four - six -
eight - ten.
And how many flowers are there?
Flowers?
Yes. Yes.
How many flowers?
A hundred?
Two hundred?
Three hundred?
I don't know.
A hundred and seven.
A hundred and eight.
A hundred and nine.
A hundred and ten.
Bob!
Can I have a rose, please?
Thank you. I like roses.
And I like you.
Oh, look!
I've got a rose.
I've got a plum
and a peach and some grapes.
A hamburger and a map.
And I've got...
a bike.
-I love you.
-And I love you.
Off we go!
No! No! No!
I love the Princess!
I love Sylvia!
A, E, I, O, U.
I love you.
A, U, O, I, E.
You love me.
A, E, I, U, O.
Off we go.
I, O, U, E, A.
Far, far away.
A, U, I, O, E.
You love me.
A, E, I, O, U.
l love you!
I love you!
The gardener
loves the Princess?
Yes! Yes!
No! No! No!
The Princess
loves the gardener?
Yes! Yes!
No! No!
Come on!
Off we go!
Follow me!
Bye!