Corvax!
Stop the computer!
I can't, your Majesty.
Of course you can.
It’s your computer.
Yes, I know.
It’s mine, but I can't stop it.
Well I can stop it.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Be careful! Be careful!
It’s all right, Corvax.
Don't do that!
Corvax! Corvax!
Help me!
Look!
-There's one!
-And there's one!
And there!
Oh, there are lots of them!
There's a fat one!
Ah, that one's fatter!
Look!
There's a big one!
That's a bigger one over there!
Come on, Muzzy!
I’m big.
I’m bigger.
The first one's big.
The second one's bigger.
I’m small.
Yes. The third one's small.
And the fourth one's smaller.
The fifth is tall.
The sixth is taller.
The seventh is... fat.
And the eighth is...
Fatter.
Help me, Corvax.
I can't, your Majesty.
Silly! You're silly!
Oh dear! What can I do?
Ah, I can run away.
Yes! The helicopter!
Help!
Help, Corvax! Corvax!
Excuse me, your Majesty.
What's happening?
Where are you going?
To the helicopter.
Help!
The King's in the computer,
Corvax.
Stop! Come back!
Corvax!
Hey, stop!
Muzzy, go up there
to the computer room!
Help the Queen.
I can stop Corvax.
Sorry!
Excuse me!
Excuse me.
Oh, I beg your pardon.
Stop! Stop!
Stop!
Who's... What's that?
It’s all right.
That's Muzzy.
He's a friend.
Muzzy, this is the Queen.
Your Majesty!
What's happening?
What's that green thing?
Oh, that's not a thing.
That's Muzzy.
He's a friend.
But he can't help!
Where's Corvax?
Ah, yes.
Corvax can help.
Corvax is clever.
No, he isn't. He's silly.
I can help, your Majesty.
You?
But you aren't clever.
I am.
Lovely!
What are you doing, Muzzy?
Wait a moment!
-What are you doing?
-Excuse me.
I’m hungry.
Hungry?
But the King's in there.
Why are you eating that?
Because I like it.
Ah, I see.
This goes here.
No, no it doesn't.
Careful, please, Muzzy!
It’s all right.
It goes in here.
And this goes in here.
All right, your Majesty.
I’m ready.
I’m ready too.
It’s hot in here.
That's better.
Thank you, Muzzy.
You are clever.
Where's Bob?
Bob? Bob the gardener?
Oh, look...
Come on, Bob!
Great!
-Well done, Bob!
-Come on!
-Great.
-Well done, Bob.
OK. We've got him.
Corvax! Corvax!
Wake up!
Why?.. What's happening?
Who are you?
Where am I?
Why am I here?
Who am I?
You are Corvax.
And you are silly.
Yes, I’m silly.
No, I’m not. I’m clever.
You are not clever, Corvax.
Take him away!
Yes, take him away!
Stand there! Now...
try this.
They're going.
They're going
into the computer.
There goes a red one.
There goes a blue.
There goes a green one.
A black and white one too.
Lots and lots of Sylvias,
coming back this way.
Three cheers for Muzzy.
Hurray! Hurray! Hurray!
Now there are ten of them.
Now there are nine.
Eight, seven, six, five,
coming on behind.
Four's going in now.
There goes number three.
Number two and number one.
-And that leaves...
-Me!
Hurray! Hurray! Hurray!
You and I are happy.
A, E, I, O, U.
Now we are together.
I love you.
Who is that beautiful girl?
What is her name?
Where does she come from?
When can I see her?
Why am I down here?
Now we are together.
I love you.
That goes in there.
This goes up here.
I don't like this job.
-That one.
-This one?
No, the big one.
Oh, dear! Oh dear!
Oh dear!
Now for that one.
This?
And that one!
What a dirty job!
Now it's lunch-time.
Yes, I'm hungry.
-Take all those away.
-Oh dear!
Oh dear! Oh dear!
Now I'm in my spaceship.
Now I'm going away.
Thank you.
Thank you, Muzzy.
Please come back some day.
Goodbye! Goodbye!
Goodbye!
We're saying goodbye
to Muzzy.
We're saying goodbye to you.
The King, the Queen,
Sylvia, Bob,
Corvax and Norman too.
Goodbye! Goodbye!