- Hi!
- Hello!
Daddy! Mummy!
Corvax!
Sylvia! Sylvia!
Oh, Mummy!
I love Princess Sylvia.
- Take him away!
Take him away!
Take him away,
take him away...
Thank you, Corvax.
- Name?
- Bob.
- Age?
- Twenty.
- Job?
- Gardener.
Take him away.
Number nineteen.
Number nineteen?
Number nineteen!
Number nineteen?..
- Nine.
- Ten.
- Eleven.
- Twelve.
- Thirteen.
- Fourteen.
- Fifteen.
- Sixteen.
Seventeen.
- Eighteen.
- Nineteen.
Twenty.
Nineteen!
A monster!
Hello.
I'm Muzzy.
Big Muzzy.
The Big Muzzy Story.
I'm hungry.
Lovely!
I like clocks.
I'm hungry.
Plums! Plums!
Lovely plums!
What's this?
It's a plum.
What?
- What's this?
- I don't know.
It's a bike.
- What's this?
- I don't know.
It's a spaceship.
- What's this?
- It's a clock.
No, it's a parking meter.
What's this?
- It's a typewriter.
- No, it's a computer.
What's this?
It's a cat.
What's that?
It's my bell.
See you!
What's this?
It's a plum. Eat it!
I don't like it!
Look. How about this?
- What is it?
- It's a peach.
Eat it!
It's lovely.
No! Horrible!
I don't like it.
It's horrible.
I don't like this
and I don't like that.
This.
That.
I don't like this
and I don't like that.
I don't like these
and I don't like those.
What's that?
- What's that thing?
- What thing?
That thing.
That thing!
It's a parking meter.
A parking meter?
Yes. You...
Lovely!
I like this!
I like parking meters.
Name?
What's your name?
Muzzy.
No, Big Muzzy.
Age?
Lovely!
Take him away,
take him away...
Hello.
Hello, monster.
I'm Muzzy.
Hello, I'm a friend.
Who are you?
What's your name?
B... B... Berb... Berb...
Bob!
Who are you?
Who?
- Who are you?
- I'm the King.
No, it isn't for you.
- Who are you?
- I'm the Queen.
No, it isn't for you.
- Who's this?
- It's the Princess!
No, it isn't for her.
- Who's that?
- It's Corvax.
- You're Corvax?
- Yes, I am.
This is for you.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Who... Who are you?
I'm Norman. Bye!
Now, who are you?
I'm Bob.
I'm a gardener.
Who are you?
Where do you come from?
There!
Up there!
Where?
There! Up there!
I come from up there.
There.
Where?
Where do you come from?
France.
Britain.
Where do you come from?
Germany.
Italy.
Where do you come from?
Greece.
And I come from Japan.
Bye!
I come from up there,
and now I'm down here.
I'm here, too.
Oh, Sylvia.
S - y - l -
v - i - a.
I love you.
B - o - b.
A - a,
B - b,
C - c,
D - d,
E - e,
F - f,
G - g,
H - h,
I - i,
J - j,
K - k,
L - l,
M - m,
N - n,
O - o,
P - p,
Q - q,
R - r,
S - s,
T - t,
U - u,
V - v,
W - w.
X - x,
Y - y,
Z - z.
- Sylvia!
- Stop it, Corvax!
Go away!
I love Bob!
I love you, Sylvia.
Oh, go away!
Stop! Sylvia!
Stop! Come here!
Oh, Sylvia! Stop!
Come here!
Corvax!
Go away!
Stop!
Come here!
Look!
Listen!
Go away.
Stop!
Come here!
Look!
Listen!
Go away!
Oh Sylvia!
Sylvia!