Is it still working?
Yes it's working.
Good evening.
How many Sylvias are there?
Six.
No, there are seven.
-Is it still raining?
-No, it's fine now.
-It's getting dark.
-What's the time?
It's nearly seven o'clock.
It gets dark at seven.
In autumn it gets
dark at seven.
Autumn?
Autumn.
Winter.
Spring.
Summer.
In autumn
it gets dark at seven.
In winter
it gets dark at five.
In spring
it gets dark at seven.
In summer
it gets dark at nine.
September.
October.
November.
December.
January.
February.
March.
April.
May.
June.
July.
August.
January. February.
March. April. May. June.
July. August. September.
Monday. Tuesday.
Wednesday. Thursday.
Friday. Saturday.
Sunday.
On Monday I play football.
On Tuesday I play basketball.
On Wednesday I go roller-
skating.
On Thursday I do my exercises.
On Friday I go swimming.
On Saturday I play golf.
And on Sunday we play tennis.
When?
When do you play football?
On Monday!
When do you play basketball?
On Tuesday!
When do you go roller-skating?
On Wednesday.
When do you do your exercises?
On Thursday.
When do you go swimming?
On Friday.
When do you play golf?
On Saturday.
When do you play tennis?
On Sunday.
And it's Sunday today.
And we're playing tennis now.
Where's Princess Sylvia's room?
-There!
-Where,
on the first floor?
No, it's on the second floor.
Oh, there are three rooms
on the second floor.
Which one is it?
-Is it the one on the left?
-No, it isn't.
-Is it the one on the right?
-Is it the one in the middle?
-Yes, it is.
It's the one in the middle.
What about the room up there?
The one on the top floor.
That's Corvax's room.
It's the computer room.
Stop it! Stop it!
No! No! No!
Food. Clocks. Seven p.m.
I've got some food.
I've got some clocks.
And it's nearly seven o'clock.
OK.
Open the door... quietly!
Look around... carefully!
Run downstairs... quickly!
Hello Sylvia!
Hello.
That's me!
Oh!
It's seven. Bob's waiting.
That's me again!
Seven o'clock!
It's dinner-time, Sylvia!
-Yes, Mummy.
Look, they're all Sylvias.
How many are there?
There are three in the kitchen.
Four in the hall.
There's one by the fireplace.
There are two against the wall.
There's one in the sitting-room
bouncing on the chairs.
And four are having lots of
fun,
sliding down the stairs.
There are hundreds in the
garden
picking all the flowers.
And lots in the bathrooms
turning on the showers.
Lots on the chandeliers.
More over there!
More of them and more of them,
appearing everywhere!
Where are they all coming from?
Look,
they're coming from Corvax's
room upstairs.
What's he doing?
Go and see... quick!
Stop it! Stop it!
Help!
Corvax!
What are you doing?
I'm not doing anything.
It's the computer.
Help!
Listen!
It's Sylvia.
Oh, Bob!
I'm frightened.
Why?
Why are you frightened?
Because there are
lots of Sylvias in the palace.
-Sylvias?
-Excuse me.
Have you got any clocks?
-Oh, Muzzy!
-Here you are.
Muzzy, why do you eat clocks?
Because I like them,
of course.
Why?
Oh, dear! He's crying.
Why are you crying?
Because I can't reach the apple.
Why can't you reach the apple?
Because I'm small.
I can reach the apple.
Yes.
-Why?
-Because you're tall.
Right!
-Here you are!
-Thanks.
Bye!
Hey! That's my apple,
and my bike.
Come back! Come back!
That's mine!
Gotcha!
Now, is this my bike?
Yes, it's yours.
Yes, it's mine.
And where's my apple?
You can't have it.
-Why not?
-Because it's in here.
Oh, Bob.
Lots of Sylvias?
Ah! I see.
Corvax!
The computer!
Bob! Where are you going?
To the computer room.
Come on!
Follow me!