Muddy Puddles
It is raining today, so Peppa and George cannot play outside.
Daddy, it's stopped raining.
Can we go out to play?
All right. Run along you two.
Peppa loves jumping in muddy puddles.
I love muddy puddles.
Peppa. if you jump in muddy puddles
you must wear your boots.
Sorry mummy.
Geogre likes to jump in muddy puddles too.
George, if you jump in muddy puddles
you must wear your boots.
Peppa likes to look after
her little brother George.
George, let's find some more puddles.
Peppa and George are having a lot of fun.
Peppa has found a little puddle.
George has found a big puddle.
Look, George,
there's a really big puddle.
George wants to jump into the big puddle first.
Stop George!
I must check if it's safe for you.
Good, it is safe for you.
Sorry George, it's only mud.
Peppa and George love jumping in muddy puddles.
Come on, George,
let's go and show Daddy.
Goodness me!
Daddy, daddy,
guess what we've been doing!
Let me think.
Have you been watching television?
No no Daddy.
Have you just have a bath?
No no.
I know,
you've been jumping in muddy puddles!
Yes yes, daddy,
we've been jumping in muddy puddles!
And look at a mess you're in.
Oh well, it's only mud.
Let's clean up quickly,
before mummy sees the mess.
Daddy, when you've cleaned up,
would you and mummy come and play too?
yes, we can all play in the garden.
Peppa and Geore are wearing their boots.
Mummy and Daddy are wearing their boots.
Peppa loves jumping up
and down in muddy puddles.
Everyone loves jumping up
Oh Daddy pig,
look at a mess you're in!
It's only mud!